http://www.eccb-centralbank.org/p/privacy-policy

Who We AreAbout UsRoles and FunctionsMember CountriesMonetary PolicyLegal and Regulatory FrameworkVideo GalleryECCB Family TimeJoin Our TeamFAQs about the ECCBContact Us What We DoFinancial StabilityRegulations and StandardsMeetings CalendarStatisticsRegional Government Securities Market (RGSM)Money and Capital MarketsCurrencyPayment SystemAbandoned PropertyGrowth and Resilience DialogueECCB Digital EC Currency Pilot Legislation How We Serve YouNews ReleasesPublicationsCommunity OutreachPublic EducationSir Cecil Jacobs AuditoriumSurveysSale of Commemorative CoinsUseful LinksEvent RegistrationECCB's COVID-19 ResponseThe Digital EconomyECCB Digital DialoguesContact Us
Thank you! Your submission has been received!
Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form
Who We Are
About UsRoles and FunctionsMember CountriesMonetary PolicyLegal and Regulatory FrameworkVideo GalleryECCB Family TimeJoin Our TeamFAQs about the ECCBContact Us What We Do
Financial StabilityRegulations and StandardsMeetings CalendarStatisticsRegional Government Securities Market (RGSM)Money and Capital MarketsCurrencyPayment SystemAbandoned PropertyGrowth and Resilience DialogueECCB Digital EC Currency Pilot Legislation How We Serve You
News ReleasesPublicationsCommunity OutreachPublic EducationSir Cecil Jacobs AuditoriumSurveysSale of Commemorative CoinsUseful LinksEvent RegistrationECCB's COVID-19 ResponseThe Digital EconomyECCB Digital DialoguesContact Us
Statistics
Publications
ECCB Connects
Join Our Team
Privacy Policy
Please read our Privacy Policy to understand how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website and app.
Who is responsible for your personal data?
The ECCB is the data controller and is responsible for the collection and processing of personal data.
Basis for the Processing of Personal Data
Personal data is collected and processed by the ECCB based on your consent. Consent is given by accepting the terms presented in the consent banner when the ECCB website or app is accessed. You can withdraw your consent at any time by submitting an email request to the ECCB using the contact details below and by removing the associated cookies from your internet browser. Instructions for the disabling of cookies can be found in our Cookie Policy. Your personal data will no longer be gathered once you have withdrawn your consent but information gathered previously will be retained.
What personal information do we collect from visitors to our blog, website or app?
When ordering coins, registering or making inquiries on our website or app, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details. We collect this information to help improve your experience. We also collect specific personal and career related data from persons who complete the relevant form for job applications on our website.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register and submit an inquiry, place an order, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter any other information on our website or app. When persons visit our website or app, third party services such as Google Analytics, LuckyOrange and Matomo are used to collect standard internet log information (such as the visitor’s IP address and browser type) and details of visitor behavior patterns.  We do this to allow us to keep track of the number of visitors that visit our website and app and to understand how our website and app are used.
In any instance where we collect your personal data, we will make this clear to you and will set out how we will use it. We will only use your personal data in a way that is compatible with the uses outlined below and we will not share your information with any other organizations for marketing, market research or commercial purposes. We do not pass on your details to other websites or apps.  The ECCB will never send out emails seeking information from anyone, unless that person has first communicated with the ECCB.  The ECCB will never send emails requesting payment to any users.
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect to:
personalize your experience when ordering coins and deliver the type of content in which you are most interested;
improve your browsing experience in order to better serve you;
respond to your customer service requests;
expedite the processing of transactions; and
follow up with visitors/applicants after correspondence.
How do we protect your information?
Your personal information is stored using secured networks and a variety of security measures are implemented when a user places an order, enters, submits or accesses information to maintain the safety of your personal information. We also perform regular vulnerability checks and malware scanning.
Personal User Data Rights
You have the right to access and rectify your personal data, to restrict the processing of your data and to ask for your data to be deleted.
Requests regarding the paragraph above should be submitted to the ECCB at info@eccb-centralbank.org.
Third-party disclosure
Our third party service providers are listed below:
Website Analytics/User Tracking: Google Analytics, LuckyOrange and Matomo
Shipping Costs: FedEx API
Merchant Bank handling collectible coin purchases: St. Kitts Nevis Anguilla National Bank
Third-party links
Our website and app may include links to other websites. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. The ECCB is not responsible or liable for the content or activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and app and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
